{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740864474","data":{"timestamp":" 946740864473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740864868","data":{"timestamp":" 946740864867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740865113","data":{"timestamp":" 946740865113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740865441","data":{"timestamp":" 946740865440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740865684","data":{"timestamp":" 946740865683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740869129","data":{"timestamp":" 946740869129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740869428","data":{"timestamp":" 946740869428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740870347","data":{"timestamp":" 946740870347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740870782","data":{"timestamp":" 946740870781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740873752","data":{"timestamp":" 946740873751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740874046","data":{"timestamp":" 946740874045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740874905","data":{"timestamp":" 946740874904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740875589","data":{"timestamp":" 946740875588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740876338","data":{"timestamp":" 946740876337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740876674","data":{"timestamp":" 946740876673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740876961","data":{"timestamp":" 946740876961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740877286","data":{"timestamp":" 946740877285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740877564","data":{"timestamp":" 946740877564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740881249","data":{"timestamp":" 946740881248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740881643","data":{"timestamp":" 946740881642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740881887","data":{"timestamp":" 946740881887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740882213","data":{"timestamp":" 946740882212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740882460","data":{"timestamp":" 946740882459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740885973","data":{"timestamp":" 946740885972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740886277","data":{"timestamp":" 946740886276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740887191","data":{"timestamp":" 946740887190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740887624","data":{"timestamp":" 946740887623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740890567","data":{"timestamp":" 946740890567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740890850","data":{"timestamp":" 946740890850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740891708","data":{"timestamp":" 946740891708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740892391","data":{"timestamp":" 946740892390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740893139","data":{"timestamp":" 946740893138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740893477","data":{"timestamp":" 946740893476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740893764","data":{"timestamp":" 946740893763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740894092","data":{"timestamp":" 946740894091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740894370","data":{"timestamp":" 946740894369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740897825","data":{"timestamp":" 946740897823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946740897940","data":{"timestamp":" 946740897939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000101_183349"," gameId":" e5a9af05-b1d9-49a5-b626-66dd518ffdac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}